Now, how to insert then, you know, at the end.
Consider a method called ad. And we are going to insert new nodes at the end, so we create struck note
had reference to now.
And this ad and a method, it contains one parameter called value of type.
And so if we are adding a new node, we should add the data inside it and this data and site it should
take into parameter and should equal to that VAT.
So how to do that?
We create struct node new node Malak.
So we are reserving the memory by creating Malak using Melcom Method.
And new node of data equal to that, we are getting the data of the new node equal to that.
OK.
We are accessing the data of the new node and putting inside it that the value of the file and argument
and putting.
So we have two cases if we are inserting a node at the end and in and new or empty link at least.
So we are considering the newly inserted one as the end and as the start and the beginning of this circle
and less.
So let's consider first, if have the equal equal to null.
Then we have a new node in the next equal to then you note, we are referring it to itself.
The next node of this node, which should be equal to that to itself because we are using and we are
dealing with circular link at least and the had equal to that new node.
So they had to refer it to that newly created one, as in you note.
So this is the beginning of the new node.
This is the beginning of that circular link, at least, and this is the end of the circular list because
the circular link at least contains only one note.
Let's consider the second case using the ELSE..
If we have a linked list that contains elements one or more nodes, then we should follow this algorithm
making a stamp equal to the head.
So I will create a temporary reference equal to the head.
And while Stamp Next does not equal to had, this is the trick behind using the circular linked list.
While Stamp next, it does not equal to the head.
While we are moving in the notes and the last note refers automatically to the first note and the first
note is the head.
So if temp equal to had if reaches the hab, so it reaches the end of the circular link, at least before
using that temp equal temp, the next we are moving the temp and temp next equal to then you note and
new note in next equal to the hat.
How to do that this is animate.
This animation will execute this ALS state where remove the binding we create.
Then you note we refer to the new note we link it with next to it, which is 2024, which is the address
of that newly created and node.
And we link the last note that we have created to the first note that we have the head pointer to it.
OK.
This time, complexity of doing such operation in central a linked list is time complexity of one as
best case scenario.
We are inserting a note into an empty list, so it is the first note that you insert and it will cost
you constant time, which is one.
While the worst case scenario is inserting none in none empty less, this is the LC statement, so the
worst case is off and we consider have one million notes and you are inserting one node at the end.
So this node will be the the pointer will traverse all the nodes $1 million node and it will insert
it at the end.
So this depend on the number of the notes.
Therefore, it is time complexity is worst case and it is of and depending on the number of notes that
contained in.